<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index on LOTHardware</title>
    <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index on LOTHardware</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2023 | enesilhaydin</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lothardware.com.tr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flipper Zero</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/flipper-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/flipper-zero/</guid>
      <description>Description The Flipper Zero device, as documented in the insightful resource available at the provided link, is a multifunctional marvel of modern hardware hacking. It offers a diverse set of capabilities, allowing users to explore a wide range of security-related applications. By harnessing its potential, security professionals and enthusiasts can delve into tasks such as RFID and NFC analysis, remote control emulation, and much more. The Flipper Zero&amp;rsquo;s flexibility makes it an indispensable tool for both offensive and defensive cybersecurity operations, empowering users to assess vulnerabilities and enhance digital protections effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandisk Ultra 16GB</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/sandisk-ultra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/sandisk-ultra/</guid>
      <description>Description The SanDisk Ultra 16GB USB drive featuring the PS2251-03 chip is a notable inclusion due to its potential for bad USB exploitation. This particular chip, known for its versatility, can be repurposed to execute malicious activities. By leveraging its capabilities, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to manipulate the device to behave in ways contrary to its intended use. This opens doors to various cybersecurity scenarios, making it a valuable addition for examining security vulnerabilities and reinforcing defenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teensy</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/teensy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/teensy/</guid>
      <description>Description Coming soon&amp;hellip;.
Device Instance Path USB Universal Halfkay:
HID\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_0478 USB_SERIAL Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_0483 USB_DUAL_SERIAL Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_048B USB_TRIPLE_SERIAL Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_048C USB_KEYBOARDONLY Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_04D0 USB_HID Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_0482 USB_SERIAL_HID Mode:
?\VID_16C0&amp;amp;PID_0487 Author @enesilhaydin Sigma/Yara Rules Coming Soon&amp;hellip;
Product Link 1- https://www.pjrc.com/teensy/ 2- https://github.com/PaulStoffregen/cores/pull/582/commits/ea2a70eaed6b78782cd4d5d504cd0ecc79ab46f2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USB Nova</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/usb-nova/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/usb-nova/</guid>
      <description>Description Coming soon.
Device Instance Path ?\VID_16D0&amp;amp;PID_11A4 VendorID 16D0 ProductID 11A4 Class ? Author @enesilhaydin Sigma/Yara Rules Coming Soon&amp;hellip;
Product Link 1- https://usbnova.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cactus WHID</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/cactus-whid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/cactus-whid/</guid>
      <description>Description The Cactus WHID, developed by the open-source community and available on GitHub, is a covert and advanced keystroke injection device. Designed to cater to the needs of penetration testers and cybersecurity experts, this compact device discreetly disguises itself as a regular USB peripheral while harboring a completely different set of capabilities. Harnessing powerful scripting features and preloaded payloads, the Cactus WHID can swiftly execute intricate and covert operations on target systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hak5 Rubber Ducky</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/hak5-rubber-ducky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/hak5-rubber-ducky/</guid>
      <description>Description The Rubber Ducky, crafted by Hak5, is a discreet and highly sophisticated keystroke injection tool. Designed for advanced penetration testers and security professionals, this pocket-sized device masquerades as a standard USB flash drive but operates with an entirely different purpose. Leveraging advanced scripting capabilities and preloaded payloads, the Rubber Ducky can execute complex and covert attacks on target systems with lightning speed. Its ability to inject keystrokes, mimic human typing patterns, and execute payloads in milliseconds makes it an invaluable asset for security assessments, uncovering vulnerabilities, and strengthening digital defenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logitech Unifying Receiver</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/logitech-unifying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/logitech-unifying/</guid>
      <description>Description First and foremost, it&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this capability functions by exploiting the CVE-2019-13052 vulnerability. Many contemporary Logitech products incorporate the Unifying feature, which proves to be highly versatile. This functionality allows for up to six pairing processes to be carried out using a Unifying Receiver, which can be particularly useful in scenarios where the primary receiver is damaged or lost. In essence, the process revolves around leveraging this vulnerability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nordic NRF52840</title>
      <link>https://lothardware.com.tr/nordic-nrf52840/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lothardware.com.tr/nordic-nrf52840/</guid>
      <description>Description First and foremost, it&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this capability functions by exploiting the CVE-2019-13052 vulnerability. Many contemporary Logitech products incorporate the Unifying feature, which proves to be highly versatile. This functionality allows for up to six pairing processes to be carried out using a Unifying Receiver, which can be particularly useful in scenarios where the primary receiver is damaged or lost. In essence, the process revolves around leveraging this vulnerability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
